DINESH AWTANI

GRAPHIC DESIGNER



CONTACT

+91 83 87 833 999

✓ dineshawtaniblogs@gmail.com

Q Jaipur, Rajasthan, INDIA

Awtani.co

PROFILE

I'm Creative Designer, I have 2 years of experience in character illustration designing & building graphics for social media & business needs. Currently working at Xpert Net Technologies Pvt Ltd as a Graphic Designer & Front-end Wordpress Designer.

Over the years I have worked with a wide variety of clients, ranging from Advertising Agencies, Retail Enterprises, Design Studios, and even Public Personalities.

SKILLS

- Graphics Design
- Design Thinking
- Illustration Scene Creation
- Front End Design
- Problem-Solving
- Social Media Design
- Project Management
- Strong Communication

EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER & FRONT-END WORDPRESS DESIGNER

Xpert Net Technologies Private Limited, Jaipur

2021 - Present

- Working as a Graphic Designer & Front-End WordPress/Shopify Developer & Designer.
- Helping Clients with illustrations & Social Media Posts.

FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER / BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT MANAGER

Herboage, Jaipur

2019 - 2021

- Worked as a Graphic Designer & WordPress Developer.
- Created brand identity & Social Media Presence.
- Website development using WordPress CMS.
- Business development manager to handle clients & projects.

NETWORK ENGINEER

Genpact India Private Limited, Jaipur 2017 - 2021

 Worked at Genpact India Pvt Ltd, Jaipur which also helped me in improving my communication skills & i learned about leadership, hardware connectivity & basic ethics.

EDUCATION

GRADE / SCHOOL

OPEN SCHOOL

2011 - 2014

GRADUATION / BACHELOR'S

Bachelor's in Computer Application, JECRC University

2014 - 2017